<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.audex.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Audeks</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAudexxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Audex</name>
  <summary>Grab the audio from your CD-ROMs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Captura l'àudio dels CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Captura l'àudio dels CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Kopírovat hudbu ze svých CD-ROMů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Ekpreni la aŭdaĵon de viaj KD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Extraiga el sonido de sus CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Harrapatu audioa zure CD-ROMetatik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Transférer les pistes audio à partir de vos CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Sasi (grab) le audio ex tu CD-Roms</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Estrai l'audio dai tuoi CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">დაითრიეთ აუდიო თქვენი CD-ROM-ებიდან</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Haal de audio uit uw CD-ROM's</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zgraj dźwięk ze swoich płyt CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Zgrabite zvok iz svojih CD-ROM-ov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">CD-ROM’larınızdaki sesleri bilgisayarınıza aktarın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Отримання звукових даних з ваших компакт-дисків</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxGrab the audio from your CD-ROMsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">从您的 CD-ROM 获取音频</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Audex is an CD ripper application. It lets you extract the audio from
      your CD-ROMs to let you listen to them on your computer and your other
      devices. It includes a CDDB and a MusicBrainz integration to fetch the
      metadata and covers for your CD-ROMs if available.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Audex és una aplicació d'extracció de CD. Permet extreure l'àudio dels CD-ROM per a permetre escoltar-los en l'ordinador i en altres dispositius. Inclou una integració amb el CDDB i el MusicBrainz per a obtenir les metadades i caràtules dels CD-ROM si estan disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Audex és una aplicació d'extracció de CD. Permet extraure l'àudio dels CD-ROM per a permetre escoltar-los en l'ordinador i en altres dispositius. Inclou una integració amb CDDB i MusicBrainz per a obtindre les metadades i caràtules dels CD-ROM si estan disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Audex estas KD-ripper-aplikaĵo. Ĝi ebligas al vi ĉerpi la audaĵon de viaj KD-ROM por ebligi vin aŭskulti ilin en via komputilo kaj viaj aliaj aparatoj. Ĝi inkluzivas CDDB kaj MusicBrainz-integriĝon por preni la metadatenojn kaj kovriloj por viaj KD-ROM se disponeblaj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Audex es una aplicación para extraer sonido de CD. Le permite extraer el sonido de sus CD para escucharlo en su equipo o en otros dispositivos. Incluye integración con CDDB y MusicBrainz para obtener metadatos y portadas de CD, si están disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Audex, CDtik erauzteko aplikazio bat da. Zure CD-ROMetatik musika atera, eta zure ordenagailuan eta beste gailu batzuetan entzuteko aukera ematen dizu. Erabilgarri daudenean, zure CD-ROMei buruzko meta-datuak eta azalak ekartzeko, CDDB eta MusicBrainz-ekin bateratzeko aukera du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Audex est une application de copie de CD. Elle vous permet d’extraire des pistes audio de vos CD-ROM afin de les écouter sur votre ordinateur et sur vos autres périphériques. Elle inclut une connexion « CDDB » et une intégration avec MusicBrainz pour trouver les métadonnées et les jaquettes de vos CD-ROM, si elles sont disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Audex es un application per rippar. Il te permitte extraher le audio ex tu CD-Roms, te permitte ascoltar los sur tu computator e sur tu altere dispositivos. Illo include un CDDB e un integration de MusicBrainz pro trovar metadatos e coperturas per tu CD-Roms, si disponibile.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Audex è un'applicazione per l'estrazione dai CD. Ti permette di estrarre l'audio dai tuoi CD-ROM e di ascoltarlo sul tuo computer e gli altri tuoi dispositivi. Include un'integrazione a CDDB e MusicBrainz per il recupero dei metadati e le copertine dei tuoi CD, se disponibili.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">'Audex' CD-დან რიპინგის აპლიკაციაა. ის საშუალებას გაძლევთ, თქვენი CD-ROM-ებიდან აუდიო გამოიღოთ და კომპიუტერზე ან სხვა მოწყობილობაზე უსმინოთ. ის ასევე შეიცავს CDDB და MusicBrainz-ის ინტეგრაციას, რომ მეტამონაცემები და ყდები გადმოწეროთ თქვენი აუდიო-CD-ებისთვის, თუ ისინი ხელმისაწვდომია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Audex is een toepassing voor cd-rippen. Het laat u de audio uit uw CD-ROM's halen om u er naar te laten luisteren op uw computer en uw andere apparaten. Het omvat een CDDB en een MusicBrainz integratie om de metagegevens en hoezen op te halen voor uw CD-ROM's indien beschikbaar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Audex to aplikacja do zgrywania z płyt CD. Umożliwia zgranie z nich dźwięku, aby móc go później słuchać na komputerze i innych urządzeniach. Obsługuje CDDB oraz MusicBrainz do pobierania metadanych i okładek, jeśli takie są dostępne dla danej płyty CD.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Audex je aplikacija za zajemanje CD-jev. Omogoča vam ekstrahiranje zvoka iz vaših CD-ROM-ov, da vam omogoča poslušanje na računalniku in drugih napravah. Vključuje integracijo CDDB in MusicBrainz za pridobivanje metapodatkov in ovitkov za vaše CD-ROM-e, če so na voljo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Audeks bir ses CD’si aktarıcısı uygulamadır. CD-ROM’larınızdan sesleri çıkarmanıza ve onları bilgisayarınızda veya başka bir aygıtınızda dinlemenize olanak tanır. Kullanılabiliyorsa CD-ROM’larınızın kapak bilgisini ve sanatçı/şarkı üst verisini almanızı sağlamak için CDDB ve MusicBrainz tümleştirmesi sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Audex — програма для видобування звукових даних з компакт-дисків. За її допомогою ви можете видобувати звукові дані з компакт-дисків для прослуховування на комп'ютері та інших ваших пристроях. Програму інтегровано з CDDB та MusicBrainz для отримання метаданих та зображень обкладинок компакт-дисків, якщо такі доступні.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAudex is an CD ripper application. It lets you extract the audio from your CD-ROMs to let you listen to them on your computer and your other devices. It includes a CDDB and a MusicBrainz integration to fetch the metadata and covers for your CD-ROMs if available.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Audex是一个 CD ripper 应用程序。 它可以让您从CD-ROM中提取音频，让您在计算机和其他设备上收听音频。 它包含一个 CDDB 和 MusicBrainz 集成，以便为您的 CD-ROM 获取元数据和封面（如果可用）。</p>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audex/audex.png</image>
      <caption>Main view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní pohled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefa vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikuspegi nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მთავარი ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok główny</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavni pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ana görünüm</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">主界面</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/audex</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=audex&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=audex</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <provides>
    <binary>audex</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.audex.desktop</launchable>
</component>
