<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.audex.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAudexxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Audex</name>
  <summary>An easy to use audio CD ripping application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una aplicació d'extracció dels CD d'ús senzill</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una aplicació d'extracció dels CD d'ús senzill</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Et brugervenligt program til at rippe cd'er</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Eine einfach zu bedienende Anwendung zum Auslesen von Audio-CDs.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">An easy to use audio CD ripping application</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una aplicación de extracción de CD de sonido fácil de usar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Hõlpsasti kasutatav heli-CD-de rippimise rakendus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Helppokäyttöinen CD:n purkusovellus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une application d'extraction de CD audio facile à utiliser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Unha aplicación de copia de CD de son fácil de usar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Sebuah kemudahan untuk menggunakan aplikasi perabitan CD audio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un'applicazione per l'estrazione dei CD audio semplice da usare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">쉽게 사용 가능한 오디오 CD 추출 프로그램</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een gemakkelijk te gebruiken audio-CD toepassing voor rippen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Łatwa w użyciu aplikacja do zgrywania płyt CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Uma aplicação de extracção de CD's de áudio simples de usar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um aplicativo fácil de usar para copiar CDs de áudio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Aplicație simplă pentru extragerea discurilor audio</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Jednoduchá aplikácia na ripovanie CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Preprosta aplikacije za pretvorbo zvočnih CD-jev</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Ett lättanvänt program för cd-lagring</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Проста у користуванні програма для видобування даних зі звукових компакт-дисків</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxAn easy to use audio CD ripping applicationxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">簡單易用的音訊 CD 擷取應用程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      The general usage of Audex is self-explanatory. With the first start Audex
      scans your system for common encoders and creates a common set of profiles
      automatically for you.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'ús general de l'Audex és autoexplicatori. Al primer inici, l'Audex explora el sistema cercant els codificadors usuals i crea automàticament un conjunt normal de perfils.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'ús general de l'Audex és autoexplicatori. Al primer inici, l'Audex explora el sistema cercant els codificadors usuals i crea automàticament un conjunt normal de perfils.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Den generelle brug af Audex er selvforklarende. Ved første start scanner Audex dit system for almindelige indkodere og opretter automatisk et almindeligt sæt profiler til dig.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Anwendung von Audex ist selbsterklärend. Beim ersten Start durchsucht Audex Ihr System nach gängigen Kodierern und erstellt automatisch einen gemeinsamen Satz von Profilen für Sie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The general usage of Audex is self-explanatory. With the first start Audex scans your system for common encoders and creates a common set of profiles automatically for you.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El uso general de Audex es autoexplicativo. La primera vez que se inicia Audex busca en el sistema codificadores comunes y crea una conjunto de perfiles comunes de forma automática.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Audexi kasutamine peaks üldiselt olema iseenesest mõistetav. Esmakäivitusel uurib Audexi süsteemis leiduvaid levinud kodeerijaid ja loob sulle automaatselt mitmed üldised profiilid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Audexin yleisen käytön tulisi olla itsestäänselvää. Ensikäynnistyksellä Audex etsii järjestelmästä koodausohjelmia ja luo automaattisesti yleisen profiilijoukon.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'utilisation de base de Audex est extrêmement intuitive. Lors de son premier démarrage, Audex scanne votre système à la recherche des encodeurs les plus utilisés et crée automatiquement une liste de profils génériques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O uso xeral de Audex é moi intuitivo. No primeiro inicio Audex examina o sistema en busca de codificadores comúns e crea automaticamente un conxunto común de perfís.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Penggunaan umum Audex adalah cukup jelas. Dengan pemulaian pertama, Audex memindai sistemmu untuk pengenkode pada umumnya dan menciptakan set profil pada umumnya secara otomatis untukmu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">L'uso generale di Audex è autoesplicativo. Al primo avvio Audex ricerca nel sistema i codificatori più comuni, e crea automaticamente un insieme comune di profili.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Audex의 일반적인 사용은 어렵지 않습니다. Audex를 처음으로 시작하면 시스템을 검사하여 인코더 설치 여부를 확인하고 적합한 프로필을 생성합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het algemene gebruik van Audex verklaart zichzelf. Bij de eerste keer starten van Audex scant uw systeem naar gemeenschappelijke encoders en maakt een gemeenschappelijke set van profielen automatisch voor u aan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ogólne przeznaczenie Audex rozumie się samo przez się. Po pierwszym uruchomieniu, Audex przegląda system w poszukiwaniu powszechnych enkoderów i tworzy powszechne profile gotowe do użytku.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O uso geral do Audex é relativamente simples. No primeiro arranque, o Audex sonda o seu sistema à procura de codificadores e cria automaticamente um conjunto comum de perfis para si.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O uso geral do Audex é auto-explicativo. Com a primeira inicialização, o Audex examina seu sistema em busca de codificadores comuns e cria automaticamente um conjunto de perfis para você.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Utilizarea generală a Audex este intuitivă. La prima pornire, Audex vă scanează sistemul pentru codori comuni și creează automat un set de profile pentru dumneavoastră.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Splošna uporaba Audexa je samoumevna. S prvim zagonom Audex pregleda vaš sistem za skupne enkoderje in samodejno ustvari skupni niz profilov za vas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Den allmänna användningen av Audex är självförklarande. När Audex startas för första gången söker det igenom systemet efter vanliga kodare och skapar automatisk en uppsättning av vanliga profiler åt dig.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Загальні принципи користування Audex є доволі очевидними. Під час першого запуску Audex виконує пошук у вашій системі типових засобів кодування і автоматично створює типовий набір профілів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe general usage of Audex is self-explanatory. With the first start Audex scans your system for common encoders and creates a common set of profiles automatically for you.xx</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source" width="664" height="566">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audex/audex.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/Audex</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>audex</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
