<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.audex.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <name>Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Audeks</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxAudexxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Audex</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Audex</name>
  <summary>Grab the audio from your CD-ROMs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Captura l'àudio dels CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Captura l'àudio dels CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Kopírovat hudbu ze svých CD-ROMů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Grab the audio from your CD-ROMs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Ekpreni la aŭdaĵon de viaj KD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Extraiga el sonido de sus CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Harrapatu audioa zure CD-ROMetatik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kaappaa ääni CD-ROM-levyiltä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Transférer les pistes audio à partir de vos CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Extraia o son dos seus CD-ROM.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">לכידת קטעי השמע מהתקליטורים שלך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Rögzítse a hangot CD-ROM-jairól</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Sasi (grab) le audio ex tu CD-Roms</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Estrai l'audio dai tuoi CD-ROM</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">დაითრიეთ აუდიო თქვენი CD-ROM-ებიდან</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Haal de audio uit uw CD-ROM's</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Zgraj dźwięk ze swoich płyt CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Zgrabite zvok iz svojih CD-ROM-ov</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Hämta ljud från cd-rom</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">CD-ROM’larınızdaki sesleri bilgisayarınıza aktarın</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Отримання звукових даних з ваших компакт-дисків</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxGrab the audio from your CD-ROMsxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">抓取 CD-ROM 中的音频</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">從您的 CD-ROM 光碟取出音訊</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Audex is a CD ripper application. It lets you extract the audio from
      your CDs to let you listen to them on your computer and your other
      devices. It includes CDDB and MusicBrainz integrations to fetch the
      metadata and covers for your CDs if available.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'Audex és una aplicació d'extracció de CD. Permet extreure l'àudio dels CD per a permetre escoltar-los en l'ordinador i en altres dispositius. Inclou una integració amb el CDDB i el MusicBrainz per a obtenir les metadades i caràtules dels CD si estan disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Audex és una aplicació d'extracció de CD. Permet extraure l'àudio dels CD per a permetre escoltar-los en l'ordinador i en altres dispositius. Inclou una integració amb CDDB i MusicBrainz per a obtindre les metadades i caràtules dels CD si estan disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Audex is a CD ripper application. It lets you extract the audio from your CDs to let you listen to them on your computer and your other devices. It includes CDDB and MusicBrainz integrations to fetch the metadata and covers for your CDs if available.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Audex estas KD-ripper-aplikaĵo. Ĝi ebligas al vi ĉerpi la audaĵon de viaj KD-ROM por ebligi vin aŭskulti ilin en via komputilo kaj viaj aliaj aparatoj. Ĝi inkluzivas CDDB- kaj MusicBrainz-integriĝon por preni la metadatenojn kaj kovriloj por viaj KD-ROM se disponeblaj.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Audex es una aplicación para extraer sonido de CD. Le permite extraer el sonido de sus CD para escucharlo en su equipo o en otros dispositivos. Incluye integración con CDDB y MusicBrainz para obtener metadatos y portadas de CD, si están disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Audex, CDtik ateratzeko aplikazio bat da. Zure CDetatik musika erauzi, eta zure ordenagailuan eta beste gailu batzuetan entzuteko aukera ematen dizu. CDDB eta MusicBrainz bateratuta dakartza, Erabilgarri daudenean, zure CDei buruzko meta-datuak eta azalak ekartzeko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Audex est une application de copie de CD. Elle vous permet d'extraire des pistes audio de vos CD afin que vous puissiez les écouter sur votre ordinateur et sur vos autres périphériques. Elle intègre une connexion avec la base de données « CDDB » et une interface avec MusicBrainz pour retrouver les métadonnées et les jaquettes de vos CD, si elles sont disponibles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Audex é unha aplicación de extracción de son. Permítelle extraer o son dos seus cedés para poder escoitalos no seu computador e noutros dispositivos. Inclúe integración con CDDB e MusicBrainz para obter os metadatos e as portadas dos seus cedés se están dispoñíbeis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">Audex הוא יישום להעתקה מתקליטורים. הוא מאפשר לך לחלץ את השמע מהתקליטורים שלך כדי להאזין להם במחשב ובמכשירים האחרים שלך. כולל שילוב מול CDDB ו־MusicBrainz כדי למשוך את נתוני העל ועטיפות התקליטורים שלך אם זמינים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Az Audex egy CD-beolvasó alkalmazás. Lehetővé teszi a hanganyagok kinyerését CD-kről, hogy meghallgathassa azokat számítógépén vagy más eszközein. A CDDB és MusicBrainz integrációnak köszönhetően lekérdezi a CD-k metaadatait és borítóit, ha azok elérhetők.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Audex es un application per rippar CD. Il te permitte extraher le audio ex tu CDs, te permitte ascoltar los sur tu computator e sur tu altere dispositivos. Illo include integrationes de  CDDB e de MusicBrainz pro trovar metadatos  e coperturas per tu CDs, si disponibile.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Audex è un'applicazione per l'estrazione dai CD. Ti permette di estrarre gli audio dai tuoi CD, e di ascoltarli sul tuo computer o su altri dispositivi. Include un'integrazione con CDDB e MusicBrainz per il recupero dei metadati e le copertine dei tuoi CD, se disponibili.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">'Audex' CD-დან რიპინგის აპლიკაციაა. ის საშუალებას გაძლევთ, თქვენი CD-ROM-ებიდან აუდიო გამოიღოთ და კომპიუტერზე ან სხვა მოწყობილობაზე უსმინოთ. ის ასევე შეიცავს CDDB და MusicBrainz-ის ინტეგრაციას, რომ მეტამონაცემები და ყდები გადმოწეროთ თქვენი CD-ებისთვის, თუ ისინი ხელმისაწვდომია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Audex is een toepassing voor cd-rippen. Het laat u de audio uit uw cd's halen om u er naar te laten luisteren op uw computer en uw andere apparaten. Het omvat CDDB- en MusicBrainz-integratie om de metagegevens en hoezen op te halen voor uw cd's indien beschikbaar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Audex to aplikacja do zgrywania z płyt CD. Umożliwia zgranie z nich dźwięku, aby móc go później słuchać na komputerze i innych urządzeniach. Obsługuje CDDB oraz MusicBrainz do pobierania metadanych i okładek, jeśli takie są dostępne dla danej płyty CD.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Audex je aplikacija za zajemanje CD-jev. Omogoča vam ekstrahiranje zvoka s CD-jev, da jih lahko poslušate na računalniku in drugih napravah. Vključuje integracijo s CDDB in MusicBrainz za pridobivanje metapodatkov in ovitkov za vaše CD-je, če so na voljo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Audex är ett cd-lagringsprogram. Det låter dig extrahera ljud från cd-skivor för att kunna lyssna på dem på datorn och andra apparater. Det inkluderar integration med CDDB och MusicBrainz för att hämta metadata och omslag för cd-skivor om tillgängliga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Audeks bir ses CD’si aktarıcısı uygulamadır. CD’lerinizden sesleri çıkarmanıza ve onları bilgisayarınızda veya başka bir aygıtınızda dinlemenize olanak tanır. Kullanılabiliyorsa CD’lerinizin kapak bilgisini ve sanatçı/şarkı üst verisini almanızı sağlamak için CDDB ve MusicBrainz tümleştirmesi sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Audex — програма для видобування звукових даних з компакт-дисків. За її допомогою ви можете видобувати звукові дані з компакт-дисків для прослуховування на комп'ютері та інших ваших пристроях. Програму інтегровано з CDDB та MusicBrainz для отримання метаданих та зображень обкладинок компакт-дисків, якщо такі доступні.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAudex is a CD ripper application. It lets you extract the audio from your CDs to let you listen to them on your computer and your other devices. It includes CDDB and MusicBrainz integrations to fetch the metadata and covers for your CDs if available.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Audex是一款 CD 抓轨应用程序。您可以使用它提取 CD 音频，以便在电脑或者其他设备上欣赏。它集成了 CDDB 和 MusicBrainz，可以为您的 CD 获取元数据和封面 (如果可用)。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">Audex 是一個 CD 擷取器應用程式。Audex 讓您從 CD 光碟取出音訊資料，讓您能在自己的電腦與其他裝置上不需要光碟也能繼續聆聽。Audex 提供與 CDDB 及 MusicBrainz 的整合，來取得 CD 的中繼資料與封面（如果有的話）。</p>
  </description>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/audex/audex.png</image>
      <caption>Main view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Hlavní pohled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Main view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Ĉefa vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ikuspegi nagusia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Päänäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista principal.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגה ראשית</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Fő nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista principal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista principale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მთავარი ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Hoofdweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok główny</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Glavni pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Huvudvy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Ana görünüm</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Головне вікно</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxMain viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">主视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">主檢視</caption>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/audex</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=audex&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=audex</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <provides>
    <binary>audex</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.audex.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
  </releases>
</component>
